<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">beFast</string>
    <string name="email" translatable="false">Email</string>

    <string name="title_news">News</string>
    <string name="title_brands">Brands</string>
    <string name="title_drops">Drops</string>
    <string name="title_more">More</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="logged_in">You are logged in</string>
    <string name="logged_out">You are logged out</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="nightmode">Nightmode</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="reminder">Set Reminder</string>
    <string name="share_drop">Share this Drop</string>
    <string name="share_app">Share</string>
    <string name="homepage">Visit website</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="terms_cons">Privacy</string>
    <string name="valid_email">Please enter a valid username &amp; email.</string>
    <string name="get_app">Get the new beFast app here:</string>
    <string name="email_subject">Your Subject</string>
    <string name="email_message">Put your email message here.</string>
    <string name="internet_connection">Could not fetch data from API.</string>
    <string name="brand_error">no brand found</string>
    <string name="name_error">no name found</string>
    <string name="price_error">no price found</string>
    <string name="date_error">no date found</string>
    <string name="hompageURL_error">no homepage URL found</string>
    <string name="brands_saved">Your brands have been saved!</string>
    <string name="brands_info">You have to login to follow brands.</string>
    <string name="drops_info">Follow brands to see drops.</string>
    <string name="id1">Just two weeks after dropping them in hoodie form, Supreme has returned to release a t-shirt version of their highly-anticipated Cross Box Logo. This red Supreme Cross Box Logo t-shirt feature\'s two of the brand\'s popular box logos laid over one another in the shape of a cross. The Supreme Cross Box Logo t-shirt was released as a part of the brand\'s FW20 winter tees collection which also included the Mariah Carey t-shirt.</string>
    <string name="id2">"The Adventurer edition of the XT2 is inspired by the early days travelling overseas, from the winter gloom in Scotland to the sunshine warmth of California. Executed in a lush pig suede application, the colours reference the stark contrast  in weather whilst  a ‘memories’  print is featured on the lining."</string>
    <string name="id4">"Sail away while wearing the Air Fear Of God 1 Sail Black. This Air FOG 1 comes with a sail upper, black Nike “Swoosh”, sail midsole, and translucent sole. These sneakers were released in June 2019 and retailed for $350. BeFast for the next drop!"</string>
    <string name="id5">"Designed to interpret the colors found on the Husky Rat breed, this latest version dyes its nubuck and pigskin-engineered upper with nude and grey hues to mirror elements of its fur. Complementing tones of pink are additionally added into the forefoot overlays to translate the rodent’s other features such as its ears, paws, and tail, which ultimately result in a much brighter approach to its collection sibling."</string>
    <string name="id7">"The Nike Air Force 1 Orange Skeleton comes dressed in an all-orange leather upper with a skeleton x-ray print on each side of the upper. Similar to the candle-lit glow of a Jack-O-Lantern, this release features a glow-in-the-dark translucent sole that is geared to light up your step. Glossy black lace tags, Nike Air branding on the tongue, and a skeleton printed insole complete this spooky AF1."</string>
    <string name="id0">With the sneakers from the Rayguns collection, Nike created an incredibly good story around them, which revolved around a fantasy basketball team in space. With elaborate videos and cool marketing campaigns, the Nike Dunk came on the market at the time, now two more releases under the Rayguns flag are imminent. In addition to the Kyrie 7, a real classic awaits us with the Air Force 1, which has been subjected to the topic.</string>
    <string name="id3">The A-ZX series is entering the next round and has a ZX 5000 ready for us. The letter V from the A-ZX alphabet is dedicated to the French city of Vieux Lyon, where the well-known jacquard pattern originally came from. For this reason, the ZX 8000 was also provided with the elaborate embroidery, which is drawn in different colors over the entire sneaker. The lower area is covered with the fabric in a cool gray and the upper area is kept in a striking purple.</string>
    <string name="id6">Famous Paris Saint Germain striker Kylian Mbappe helps Lebron James with his 18th signature sneaker. The two friends publish a collaborative sneaker together. The court sneaker comes with a more futuristic look that gets a black Knitposite 2.0 upper that honors the city of France with red and blue decorations. Silver tongues as well as a translucent heel clip and an iridescent rubber outsole complete the brand new look.</string>
    <string name="id8">The first colorway of the Ambush Nike Dunk High appeared a few weeks ago, now the lethal pink, which has long been teased, is appearing. Yoon is known for her creative and individual approach and she showed this once again on her own dunk high.</string>
    <string name="id9">The year starts again with really strong colourways on the Jordan 1 High! The popular sneaker is given a color combination of black, white, neon yellow and yellow gold details. The choice of materials was based on high-quality smooth leather. In addition, the sneaker has slight vintage moments thanks to the foam tongue. The color of the foam is also golden yellow and therefore matches the color of the heel perfectly.</string>
    <string name="id10">The Air Max 97 has never been a particularly subtle sneaker. The multi-layered wave aesthetics and the continuous, visible air element were a real eye-catcher when it was released. Even 20 years later, the design of the shoe, with which the casual, corrugated upper material has been improved, is still striking.</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="privacy">Privacy</string>
    <string name="privacy_text"><b>Privacy</b>\nWelcome to beFast!\nThese terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of beFasts Website, located at www.beFast.com.
    By accessing this website we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use beFast if you do not agree to take all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.
    The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and all Agreements: "Client", "You" and "Your" refers to you, the person log on this website and compliant to the Company’s terms and conditions. "The Company", "Ourselves", "We", "Our" and "Us", refers to our Company. "Party", "Parties", or "Us", refers to both the Client and ourselves. All terms refer to the offer, acceptance and consideration of payment necessary to undertake the process of our assistance to the Client in the most appropriate manner for the express purpose of meeting the Client’s needs in respect of provision of the Company’s stated services, in accordance with and subject to, prevailing law of Netherlands. Any use of the above terminology or other words in the singular, plural, capitalization and/or he/she or they, are taken as interchangeable and therefore as referring to same.
    \n<b>Cookies</b>\nWe employ the use of cookies. By accessing beFast, you agreed to use cookies in agreement with the beFasts Privacy Policy. \n
    Most interactive websites use cookies to let us retrieve the user’s details for each visit. Cookies are used by our website to enable the functionality of certain areas to make it easier for people visiting our website. Some of our affiliate/advertising partners may also use cookies.
    \n<b>License</b>\nUnless otherwise stated, beFast and/or its licensors own the intellectual property rights for all material on beFast. All intellectual property rights are reserved. You may access this from beFast for your own personal use subjected to restrictions set in these terms and conditions.
    \nYou must not:
    Republish material from beFast
    Sell, rent or sub-license material from beFast
    Reproduce, duplicate or copy material from beFast
    Redistribute content from beFast
    This Agreement shall begin on the date hereof. Our Terms and Conditions were created with the help of the Terms And Conditions Generator and the Privacy Policy Generator.

    Parts of this website offer an opportunity for users to post and exchange opinions and information in certain areas of the website. beFast does not filter, edit, publish or review Comments prior to their presence on the website. Comments do not reflect the views and opinions of beFast,its agents and/or affiliates. Comments reflect the views and opinions of the person who post their views and opinions. To the extent permitted by applicable laws, beFast shall not be liable for the Comments or for any liability, damages or expenses caused and/or suffered as a result of any use of and/or posting of and/or appearance of the Comments on this website.
    beFast reserves the right to monitor all Comments and to remove any Comments which can be considered inappropriate, offensive or causes breach of these Terms and Conditions.

    You warrant and represent that:
    You are entitled to post the Comments on our website and have all necessary licenses and consents to do so;
    The Comments do not invade any intellectual property right, including without limitation copyright, patent or trademark of any third party;
    The Comments do not contain any defamatory, libelous, offensive, indecent or otherwise unlawful material which is an invasion of privacy
    The Comments will not be used to solicit or promote business or custom or present commercial activities or unlawful activity.
    You hereby grant beFast a non-exclusive license to use, reproduce, edit and authorize others to use, reproduce and edit any of your Comments in any and all forms, formats or media.

    Hyperlinking to our Content
    The following organizations may link to our Website without prior written approval:

    Government agencies;
    Search engines;
    News organizations;
    Online directory distributors may link to our Website in the same manner as they hyperlink to the Websites of other listed businesses; and
    System wide Accredited Businesses except soliciting non-profit organizations, charity shopping malls, and charity fundraising groups which may not hyperlink to our Web site.
    These organizations may link to our home page, to publications or to other Website information so long as the link: (a) is not in any way deceptive; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products and/or services; and © fits within the context of the linking party’s site.

    We may consider and approve other link requests from the following types of organizations:

    commonly-known consumer and/or business information sources;
    dot.com community sites;
    associations or other groups representing charities;
    online directory distributors;
    internet portals;
    accounting, law and consulting firms; and
    educational institutions and trade associations.
    We will approve link requests from these organizations if we decide that: (a) the link would not make us look unfavorably to ourselves or to our accredited businesses; (b) the organization does not have any negative records with us; © the benefit to us from the visibility of the hyperlink compensates the absence of beFast; and (d) the link is in the context of general resource information.

    These organizations may link to our home page so long as the link: (a) is not in any way deceptive; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products or services; and © fits within the context of the linking party’s site.

    If you are one of the organizations listed in paragraph 2 above and are interested in linking to our website, you must inform us by sending an e-mail to beFast. Please include your name, your organization name, contact information as well as the URL of your site, a list of any URLs from which you intend to link to our Website, and a list of the URLs on our site to which you would like to link. Wait 2-3 weeks for a response.

    Approved organizations may hyperlink to our Website as follows:
    By use of our corporate name; or
    By use of the uniform resource locator being linked to; or
    By use of any other description of our Website being linked to that makes sense within the context and format of content on the linking party’s site.
    No use of beFasts logo or other artwork will be allowed for linking absent a trademark license agreement.

    iFrames
    Without prior approval and written permission, you may not create frames around our Webpages that alter in any way the visual presentation or appearance of our Website.

    Content Liability
    We shall not be hold responsible for any content that appears on your Website. You agree to protect and defend us against all claims that is rising on your Website. No link(s) should appear on any Website that may be interpreted as libelous, obscene or criminal, or which infringes, otherwise violates, or advocates the infringement or other violation of, any third party rights.

    Your Privacy
    Please read Privacy Policy

    Reservation of Rights
    We reserve the right to request that you remove all links or any particular link to our Website. You approve to immediately remove all links to our Website upon request. We also reserve the right to amen these terms and conditions and it’s linking policy at any time. By continuously linking to our Website, you agree to be bound to and follow these linking terms and conditions.

    Removal of links from our website
    If you find any link on our Website that is offensive for any reason, you are free to contact and inform us any moment. We will consider requests to remove links but we are not obligated to or so or to respond to you directly.
    We do not ensure that the information on this website is correct, we do not warrant its completeness or accuracy; nor do we promise to ensure that the website remains available or that the material on the website is kept up to date.

    Disclaimer
    To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we exclude all representations, warranties and conditions relating to our website and the use of this website. Nothing in this disclaimer will:
    limit or exclude our or your liability for death or personal injury;
    limit or exclude our or your liability for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation;
    limit any of our or your liabilities in any way that is not permitted under applicable law; or
    exclude any of our or your liabilities that may not be excluded under applicable law.
    The limitations and prohibitions of liability set in this Section and elsewhere in this disclaimer: (a) are subject to the preceding paragraph; and (b) govern all liabilities arising under the disclaimer, including liabilities arising in contract, in tort and for breach of statutory duty.
    As long as the website and the information and services on the website are provided free of charge, we will not be liable for any loss or damage of any nature.</string>
    <string name="note_saved">Note saved.</string>
    <string name="username_empty">Username can not be empty.</string>
    <string name="no_valid_email">No valid email address.</string>
</resources>